{
    "id": "0ffd6f4612d1440ab8a53ef10ad0d50e",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Who will ……………………………… the drinks?",
            "description": "We pay for something that is bought.",
            "answers": [
                "pay",
                "pay for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1a10a318c5ed43b69149f243d97cdf7d"
        },
        {
            "question": "He wasn’t very nice ……………………………. me when we met yesterday.",
            "description": "With is not used after words which say how people act towards others.",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2e79884b04fa4e3d8e53496f4c57cc5c"
        },
        {
            "question": "The noise prevented me …………………………….",
            "description": "Prevent is followed by object + from + ing form.",
            "answers": [
                "of working",
                "to work",
                "from working"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "83602d58a46640f48d9b8eb1072ed510"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is rude ……………………………… everyone.",
            "description": "With is not used after words which say how people act towards others.",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4422d5cc375d42489edc6ef0f22b8ea3"
        },
        {
            "question": "The police ………………………………….. everybody’s luggage.",
            "description": "When search is used without preposition, it means look through.",
            "answers": [
                "searched",
                "searched for"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "786cda7aafc343478c83f8d486892afe"
        },
        {
            "question": "The police are ………………………………. a bald guy in his thirties.",
            "description": "Search for means the same as look for.",
            "answers": [
                "searching",
                "searching for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "20ced911699d4d499c973716876efee2"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was shocked ………………………………… the news of the accident.",
            "description": "Either by or at can be used after shocked.",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "by",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "96b50dd6684a4bd1869be2c5f2983efe"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is quite pleased …………………………………. his results.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "about",
                "at",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "59da008a00ce4cd4b2cc65d5f7444c59"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am thinking ………………………………… studying palmistry.",
            "description": "Either about or of is possible here. To is not possible. ",
            "answers": [
                "about",
                "of",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4d6c9006459847948d139ab8ba3febe2"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is polite ………………………………. everyone.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a17043a6acb147a29f2d316c13db67c0"
        },
        {
            "question": "What does it mean if you dream …………………………………… hills and valleys?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "about",
                "of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a9d3af59ebf24e55be0e3ce7691e8126"
        },
        {
            "question": "The driver was sleeping and crashed …………………………………. the car in front.",
            "description": "We usually say crash into. ",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "into",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f1239bfad2334a50a7e0c90519248e59"
        }
    ]
}